Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files
1912-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees (NUHHCE)
Local 1199 Drug amd Hospital Union
6169
12 cubic feet
12 linear ft.
Records.
5830509
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 20, 2004
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5929: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Records 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6085 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project "Frederick Douglass and His Time" Posters 6089 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Posters 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs
Working class--Songs and music; Women--United States; Fasanella, Ralph; Foner, Moe, 1915-; King, Coretta Scott, 1927-2006; King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1929-1968; Bread and Roses Cultural Project; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees.; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.)
5830509
- Moe Foner Files (Box 1)
  - "Take Care" Files: 1 of 2, 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Posters, Articles, Flyers and Invitations to Exhibitions
  - "Take Care" Files: 2 of 2, 1972-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gallery and District 1199 Exhibitions, 1972-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Pamphlets and Flyers for Various Exhibitions
  - Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Newspaper Clippings on Health Care Crisis, Letters from Local 1199 and Rally Posters
  - Chapter 6, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    BREAD AND ROSES: Working People Deserve the Best in "Not For Bread Alone" by Moe Foner
  - Chapter 7, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    SAVE OUR UNION: The Fight to Preserve 1199's Ideals in "Not For Bread Alone" by Moe Foner
  - Chapter 8, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    SENIOR ADVISOR: Passing It On in "Not For Bread Alone" by Moe Foner
  - Grant Applications for William Serrin Book, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Newspaper Clippings and Donations for Serrin's Bread and Roses Cultural Project
  - Labor Quotes (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Loose Leaf Paper with Handwritten and Typed Quotes
  - Passport: Ellis Island, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Postal Mailings for Ellis Island Immigration Museum
  - Calendar Chrome and Examples, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Working People: The Art of Ralph Fasanella
  - Exhibition Fasanella, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Delegates' Reception on Friday November 17, 2000 from 5:30-7:00PM
  - Moe Meetings: Notes, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    On Fasanella Calendar Distribution and Sales
  - Bread and Roses Press Kit, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Flyers, Programs and Newspaper Press
  - Conference - Not Bread Alone, 1968-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Maj Britt Theorin, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Correspondences
  - Women of Hope, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Series of Posters and Study Guide
  - Reforma - 1st National Conference, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Skipping Stones Awards
  - Photo Contract, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    International Women of Hope
  - Proposal - International Women of Hope, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Prints
  - International Women of Hope Proposal, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - International Women of Hope, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Emails for Fifth Poster Set
  - Mailing to Funders International Women of Hope, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - MLK Speech, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Permission Statement, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    For Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope
  - International Women, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Emails, Forms and Photograph
  - Correspondence - International Women of Hope, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Evaluations, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    "Not Bread Alone" Conference
  - Sexual Harassment (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Book Photocopies
  - What is a Union (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Textbook Photocopies
  - Bread and Roses/Greenhouse Catalogue (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Order Form
  - Images of Labor and Lenin Grads, 1981-1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Foner Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Original Script of Mike's Broadcast for Local 1199
  - Photos of Ralph Fasanella (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Black and White Photocopied
- Women of Hope Files (Box 2)
  - Asian, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Essay Biographies of Individuals
  - Diane - Asian, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Women of Hope Project
  - Asian File, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Asian Study Guide, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - People Who Saw the Women of Hope Posters on Subway, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Letters, Postcards and Emails
  - Sex Harassment, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Letters and Newspaper Clippings
  - Videofest, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Skipping Stones Magazine and Film Schedule
  - Vinnie Burrows, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Flyer and Descriptions Presented by 1199's Bread and Roses
  - Asian Bio Edited, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Biographies of Asian Individuals
  - Asian Bio "Quotes", 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bread and Roses, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Women of Hope: Letters, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Gates, Streinem, Painter, Cortinez, etc.
  - Letters Latina WOH, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Letters Regarding Women of Hope Campaign Posters
  - Photos - Zerox Copies (Latina WOH) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Transcript and Tape Log - Latina Videos, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    In English and Spannish
  - Video - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fingerhut Poll, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Labor Cable TV, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Native AM WOH, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Grants and Funds Applications
- Publicity Files (Box 3)
  - 1199 Newspaper Clippings, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    On Home-Care Workers
  - Agreement/Impact, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Home Care Workers
  - Health Care Workers News, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Newspaper Clippings
  - Health Care Hearing Testimony, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Of Debroah King and David Buchholz
  - Fact Sheet Home Care, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    4 Copies
  - Proposed Op-Ed a Piece/Ad, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Press Release, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Hold For Release on January 11, 1988 11AM
  - Home Care Agreement Analysis, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    February 1988
  - Newsday - Home Care Services, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Newspaper Clippings 9/27, 9/28, 9/29, 9/30
  - Home Care Video Project, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Fact Sheet
  - Home Care, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Home Care Workers of the Year, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Applications
  - Home Care, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Campaign for Justice for Home Care Workers, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Award Entries and Budget Sheets
  - Children's Make-A-Wish Foundation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    7 Years Old Craig Sherfoid
  - Photos for Lawrence 1912 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Photocopied and Black and White
  - Lawrence 1912 The Bread & Roses Strike, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    by William Cahn
  - Bills for Pictures, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Invoice
  - John Schultz Video Transcripts, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Strike of Textile Workers in Lawrence, Mass (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Photocopied Book
- Labor Song Books (Box 4)
  - Third Annual Labor Day Fair, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    District 1199
  - Special Report Supplement, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Labour and Bread and Roses
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Tape, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - In-Hospital Shows "Take Care", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "Take Care", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Booklet and Itinery
  - Coretta Scott King Speeches, 1969-1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Conference on Worker's Culture, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    11/17/82
  - Songbooks, 1948-1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    The People's Song Book, The ACTWU Song Book and the Second People's Song Book
  - Hospital and 1199 News, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Clippings
  - Local 1199 News, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Newspaper and Article Clippings
  - Hospital Strike News, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Labor Songs, 1951-1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Lyrics and Music Books
  - Exhibition Flyers, 1979-1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Bread and Roses
  - Hospitals Information, 1967-1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Moe Foner Files (Box 5)
  - Gallery Art by US. 1199 Members, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    November to December
  - Latina Gallery - Women of Hope, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    March to April
  - Gallery 1199 Sweatshops, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    May to June
  - Gallery 1199 Floor Plan, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Exhibitions Chart
  - Jim Tynan, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Exhibit
  - High School Art II, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    October to November
  - High School Gallery, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Picturing Labor, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Images of Labor Donations, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Gallery 1199 AGITPROP, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    January 13, February 18, 1993
  - Gallery 1199 "Rican/Structions" by Juan Sanchez, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    January to February
  - Jim Tynan, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Haiti, April
  - Dom Lee, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Urbanscapes, March to April
  - Videotape - Take Care III, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Miscellaneous Correspondence
  - Bread and Roses Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    January to March
  - 5% Campaign, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Installation - Town Hall, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    8/26
  - Press Release Local 1199, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    8/22
  - Cuomo Statement, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    August
  - Georgianna Johnson to Leagues, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    8/1
  - Local 1199 Negotiations, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Press Release, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    9/9
- Plays, Scripts, and Theater Files (Box 6)
  - Take Care - Script, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Like a Beautiful Child, 1960-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Like a Beautiful Child, 1959-1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Like a Beautiful Child - Current, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Photos
  - I Am Somebody, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Script
  - Charleston Strike, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bread and Roses, Too, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Count Down to a Contract, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    WCBS Script
  - We, the Members of 1199 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    First Film, Drug Union
  - Practical Dreamer (LJD), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Ten Years of Progress and Struggle, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Script/Instruction Letter
  - Anne Shore Oral History, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "Nurse Where Are You?", 1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Archives - District 1199, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Archives - Cornell University, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Moe Foner Picture (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1199 Film/Video, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1199 History Video (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Cradle Will Rock (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - I am Somebody, 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Avery Fisher Hall, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Avery Fisher Hall Program, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Avery Fisher Hall Program, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Moe Foner Correspondence (Box 7)
  - Save Our Union - Fact Sheet, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - NLRB Case, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Press Release (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - League of Voluntary Hospitals, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - U & P Press Release, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    6/26
  - NLRB v. District 1199, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Doris Turner, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Speech
  - Local 1199 Case, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Operation Facelift, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Local 1199 Investigation, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dennis & Dave (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Interview
  - D.W. Affidavit, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Sworn Affidavit of Dave White
  - D.W. - South Africa $5000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Statement by David White
  - ED Lane Press Release and Affidavit, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - D.T. - Hotline, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Doris Turner Statement on 1/16
  - Update From MF, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    1/21 From Moe Foner
  - S.I. Hospital, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Memorandum for the State Island Hospital
  - Proposed El Diario Editorial (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Song (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Farewell, Doris
  - U & P Press Release, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hispanic Press Release (Box 7, Folder 21)
    "District 1199 Hispanic Members Charge Discrimination in Union Bylaw Vote"
  - Local 1199 Lawsuit, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - League Strike Tentative Agreement, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Background - Stolen Election, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Truth, The Whole Truth, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Doris Turner News and Statements
  - Local 1199 Case, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Local 1199 Investigation, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Case and Notes
  - Leon J. Davis Tribute, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    October 5 at Avery Fisher Hall - Lincoln Center
  - Lawrence 1912: Promotion, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Discussion Guides/Film Strips/Cassettes
  - Bridges and Boundaries, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Esther Cohen and Moe Foner
  - News Reports, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Bread and Roses and Hospital Workers
  - Save Our Union Reports, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Unfair Labor Practices Charges, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Chronological Press Clips, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Bread & Roses Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    January
  - Bread and Roses (Box 7, Folder 37)
    By Moe Foner
  - Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Moe Foner: Personal Correspondence (1 of 2), 1979-1995 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Moe Foner: Personal Correspondence (2 of 2), 1982-1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Publicity Files (Box 8)
  - Media Coverage: Take Care, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Reports and Event Descriptions for Bread and Roses
  - Take Care III, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Evaluation Report and Performance Notes
  - News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    On Jackson O'Connor, Focusing Attention, Campaign to Win, Victory, Editorial Support and Ads
  - Articles, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    On Project Galleries and Take Care Program
  - Disarming Images: Art for Nuclear Disarmament, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Take Care and Bread and Roses Progress Report, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases and News Clips, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    About Hospital Unions and Bread and Roses
  - Take Care Reviews, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    On Bread and Roses Take Care Musical
  - Publicity, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    On Bread and Roses "Take Care" Program
  - In-Hospital Theater New Rican Village, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Schedule and Preview
  - In-Hospital Theater, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ossie Davis & Ruby Dee, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - In-Hospital Theater Street Theater Caravan, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Theater 1199, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1199 News Working in Hospitals: Then and Now, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    September Issue
  - The New Yorker Profiles, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    December 10
  - 1199 Youth Mentoring Program, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Summer
  - Bread & Roses Folders, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Posters, Videos, Study Guides and More
- Publicity Files (Box 9)
  - Labor Day Street Fair, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    9/3/79
  - "Take Care" Revised Script, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    2/26/80
  - Publicity, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - In-Hospital Shows Take Care, Take Care - Material, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Take Care, Take Care Schedules, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Take Care" Production (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Music Script
  - Oral History Review, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "Take Care, Take Care", 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Local 1199, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Broadcast Details
  - Local 1199, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Jan-June
  - Home Health Care Contract Campaign, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Media Campaign for Local 1199 Hospital Workers Union and the Coalition for Health Care For All New York Final Report
  - Images of Labor, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Theatre in the Hospitals, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - The Labor Theater M.B., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Sam Levenson Schedule, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - In-Hospital Schedules Howard Roberts, Labor Theater, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Los Afortunados Pamphlet, Take Care Scene Order and Ossie David and Ruby Dee Introductions
  - "I Paid My Dues", 1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Production Materials
  - Publicity Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Take Care, Take Care, 1979-1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Theater in the Hospitals "Ruby Dee", 1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Local 1199 Exhibitions, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Flyers
  - Songs of Work and Freedom, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    By Edith Fowke and Joe Glazer
  - Take Care, Take Care New Material, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - "Take Care" Material for Books, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Songs
  - Take Care, Take Care, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Take Care, Take Care Publicity, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Exhibit Files (Box 10)
  - "Take Care" Script and Music, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Take Care" IV (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Take Care" on TV News Clips, 1982-1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    9/5,6/89
  - Theater in the Hospitals - Thuli Dumakude, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Take Care III Employment Records - Cast, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Take Care III, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - National Union Convention, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - National Union Convention Gifts, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - National Union Convention Guest Speakers, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - National Union Convention, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Agenda of the Sixth Convention
  - National Union Convention, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Seventh Convention
  - Montefiore Hospital, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Prints of Pictures
  - Memorial Tribute - Elliott Godoff & Sidney Barchat, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Films of Local 1199 Walter Reade Theater, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Nov. 10, 11, 1992
  - Take Care: Background Info, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Home Fallout Shelter Info, 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Haitian Art, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Labor Murals (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Working, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Asian Show, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Contact Information
  - Asian Exhibition, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    3/98
  - Cockcroft, Eva Proposed Building Mural, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Midtown West, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Children of Hope
  - Gallery 1199 Midtown West, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Tamie Arai Exhibition, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    3/12-4/26
  - Latina Exhibition, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    The Bread and Roses Cultural Project for Women's History Month
  - Ed. Mapp Posters, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    January - February
  - Letters to Ossie, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Written by 3rd/4th Grade Children in Harlem Schools
  - Langston Hughes, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Gallery 1199 Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Gallery 1199 Women & Men of the Cloth, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    September - October
  - Gallery Puerto Rican, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Information on Gallery 1199 The Puerto Rican Diaspora
  - Frederick Douglass Travel, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Gallery 1199 Women Responds, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Notes on Chiapes Gallery, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Black Images in American Films, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Save Our Union Files (Box 11)
  - Guild Delegate Assembly, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    5/8/86
  - League Letter, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    5/19/86
  - NLRB, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    5/20/86
  - Bob Sanders Thesis "Divided We Fall", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Village Voice "Will Someone Save Our Union?", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    4/15/86
  - Village Voice "1199: An Orderly Transition?", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    5/6/86
  - Village Voice "Turner Disputes 1199 Election Result", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    5/13/86
  - Village Voice "Turner Turned Out", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    July 1, 1986
  - Philadelphia Inquirer "N.Y. Vote a Victory for Phila. Labor Leader", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    4/28/86
  - The New York Times "Head of Hospital Union Trailing in Special Vote" and "Turmoil Clouds Hospital Union as Talks Near", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    4/24/86 and 4/11/86
  - N.Y. Times "Major Changes Promised for Hospital Union", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    4/25/86
  - The New York Times Editorial "Labor's Duty to NY Health", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Saturday, May 17, 1986
  - The New York Times - Raskin "A Health Care Union", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Monday, May 19, 1986
  - New York Times "N.Y.'s Hospital Union Tries to Heal Wounds", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Sunday, June 29, 1986
  - The New York Times "Hospital and Union Begins Talks on Contract", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Sunday 9/14/86
  - New York Times AD, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    9/28/86
  - N.Y. Times "Tentative Hospital Pact for 40 Sites Reached", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    10/14/86
  - NY Times "Union's Accord With Hospitals", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    10/15/86
  - Hospitals Union President Faces Jail, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    3/19/86
  - NY Newsday "Doris Turner Foes Recruit Monitors", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    4/14/86
  - N.Y. Newsday "Insurgents Claim Win in Hospital Union Vote", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    4/24/86
  - NY Newsday "Turner Heads Union Pending Poll Probe", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    5/3/86
  - New York Newsday "Union Challenges Sue", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    Thursday, May 15, 1986
  - NY Newsday "Dissidents Denied Power", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - New York Newsday "Union Chief Guilty", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Wednesday, May 28
  - Newsday "Union Blues", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    5/30/1986
  - New York Newsday New York Times, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    Tuesday, June 24, 1986
  - Newsday "Union, Hospital Group Agree on Pact", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Monday 10/13/86
  - Newsday "Hospital Workers Cheer Pact", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - New York Newsday "A New Direction for Local 1199", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    Wednesday 11/12/86
  - Guardian "Showdown Looms for Hospital Union", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    4/9/86
  - Hartford Courant "NYC Health Care Workers Overthrow", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - In These Times "Local 1199", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    May 7-13, 1986
  - New York Magazine "Labor Pains", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    3/25/85
  - El Diario/La Prensa Editorial "Playing Turner's Game", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 35)